[Music] I
[Música]
don't know exactly what happened
no sé exactamente lo que ha pasado
silver commented neri about turbos and if you don't
silver comentó neri de turbos y si no os
worry we'll see everything is
preocupéis lo vamos a ver todo me la
prepared for me here by these well-prepared and
prepara aquí esta gente bien preparada y
well-compensated people and I'm also with a
bien compensada y estoy además con un
very nice format lion now thank you very much
formato muy bonito león ya muchas
king and a huge kiss and beautiful
gracias rey y un beso enorme y guapa
sorry we didn't think of another
perdona que no se nos ha pasado otro
plan I don't know if it will come out here but I was
plan no sé si aquí saldrá pero estuve
seeing a tweet from the stutterer as if
viendo un tweet del tartaja como
throwing in his face
echándole en cara
what plan turbo had stolen lee and
qué turbo plan la había robado lee y
now someone again it could be but
ahora alguien otra vez puede ser pero
mistaking family if it were that it would
equivocando familia si fuera eso me
seem very hardcore to me I hope it's
parecería muy hardcore
not I hope they're not going
espero que no sea espero que no vayan
after rust because it would seem very
por el óxido porque me parecería muy
hardcore to me
hardcore
this time he messed up with the turbo
esta vez metió la pata al turbo
this time this time well let's see what
esta vez esta vez bueno vamos a ver qué
happened
es lo que ha pasado
turbo plas messes up with silver
turbo plas mete la pata con silver
turbo is here and has slipped you know what's
turbo está aquí y ha patinado sabes qué
going on air you
pasa aire
know what's going on air I need an
sabes qué pasa aire que necesito un
overlay look you know what's going on here we are
overlay mira sabes que pasa hay de que
going today I'm going to commission a 9 live
vamos a hoy te voy a encargar un 9 live
from you Latina to do the animations
a ti latina que haga las animaciones
so that she can team me up with some animations
para que me haga team a unas animaciones
although we already have one animation not
aunque una animación es ya tenemos no
the threads and diesel I have
lo de los hilos y diesel tengo
configured what we need an
configurado lo que necesitamos un
overlay for twitch
overlay para twitch
with several scenes air
con varias escenas aire
because now this what I would need
porque yo ahora esto lo que necesitaría
would be to be seen here on
sería que se estuviera viendo aquí en
a smaller screen the chajá
una pantalla más pequeña el chajá aquí
up here to the spectators and watch them
arriba a los espectadores y los vigile
more and here it is apart from this screen
más y aquí se aparte de esta pantalla
that is also fine
que también está bien
apart from this screen I need more
a parte de esta pantalla necesito más
scenes
escena
and you have to do them up to
y me las tienes que hacer
here it has gone
hasta aquí os ha ido
is that I still commissioned an illustrator
es que le encargué aún a un ilustrador
that I really like some designs
que me gusta mucho unos a unos diseños
but it has happened in the last few days months have
pero ha pasado en días pasados meses han
passed a month and he has not done it so we are
pasado un mes y no me ha hecho entonces
going to have to do it ourselves, you
vamos a tener que hacerlo nosotros
know there is life or not these air
sabe hay vida o no estas aire
elsa crazy that I am but in chat mode
elsa pirado que estoy pero en modo chat
because he does not see anything because the stream goes to
porque no ve nada porque el stream va a
1080 let's see if he accepts me in the partner
1080 a ver si me acepta en el partner
well nothing air that I was saying that
pues nada aire que estaba diciendo que
this would have to be made into a novel there is
esto habría que hacer una novela hay
different for when we see things in
diferente para cuando veamos cosas en
full screen
pantalla completa
because there are things for which
porque hay cosas para que queda bien
this scene looks good and there are others for which it does not
esta escena y hay otras para las que no
so a little frame in a
entonces un marquito de un estilo de
youtube style is worth it
youtube si vale
because now so that the action can be seen
porque ahora para que se viera la acción
the face that we have put
está completa la carita que hemos puesto
everything flat right now a
todo plano ahora mismo ha salido un
turbo video has come out where in his video he says
vídeo de turbo donde en su vídeo dice
that  who has scammed silver to his
que que ha estafado es silver a sus
followers comfort
seguidores confort
hello
hola
[Music]
[Música]
specifically to the followers
específicamente a los seguidores
really this is not like that who has
realmente esto no es así quién ha
lost silver's money and said that he will
perdido el dinero de silver y dijo que
put the profits out of his pocket
pondrá de su bolsillo lo de las
to do the raffles for turbo
ganancias para hacer los sorteos a la
the chevitú see
el chevitú ver
scammed
estafó
more than 160 thousand dollars from his followers
más de 160 mil dólares a sus seguidores
with the FT
con el ft
and on top of that he steals it
y encima la roba
very regrettable
muy lamentable
today ebro inform yourself better
hoy ebro infórmate mejor
that it is not that turbo plana already stole him and
que no es que turbo plana ya robaba él y
I
yo
have to turbo plague already steals trouble
tienes que turbo plaga ya roba lío
but when he doesn't steal lyon makes his
sino que cuando no roba lyon le salen
videos come out like this what a mess he is he is in trouble
así los vídeos vaya metido está de pata
and throws [ __ ] at silver I
y tira de [__] al silver
withdraw this photo
retiro de esta foto
some salt channels are or are
algunos canales de sal se o se están
making fun of turbo's blunder or
burlando de la metida de pata de turbo o
blaming that he has not investigated well
recriminando que no ha investigado bien
on the subject for example the south who has
sobre el tema por ejemplo el sur que ha
recorded a video and so many on twitter
grabado un vídeo y tantas en twitter
with the question record them and is
con la pregunta grabarlos y está
recording let me remove this [ __ ]
grabando déjenme quito esta chingadera
because if not it wasn't those guys
porque si no no eran esos güeyes
in minutes they are throwing [ __ ] and
en minutos están tirando [__] y
we believed that it was
creíamos que era
the right one not to put on the
la acertada que no ponernos de los
minutes [ __ ] that I have  that swallow
minutos cabrón que me tengo que tragar
the whole video dude
el vídeo entero tío
as I get attracted to the psychic he tries it - ha
como me atraiga el vidente lo trata -ha
me for about two minutes to see here
yo por lo de dos minutos a ver por aquí
and this yes well it does not surprise me but
y esto sí bueno no me sorprende pero
cappa and the capable and I tell you another thing
cappa y el capaz y os digo otra cosa
capable and the white turbo of the
capaz y el turbo blanco de la
information of another medley of channels and
información de otro popurrí de canales y
has mounted of his video
se ha montado de su vídeo
everything would be to look for it to surprise
todo sería buscarlo a sorprender
turbo flanders dude
turbo flandes güey
uploaded a video today talking
subió un vídeo el día de hoy hablando
about silver and his mts
sobre lo de silver y sus mts
and the title stevie you see scammed 160,000
y el título stevie tu ver estafó 160.000
dollars from his followers with nfc silver
dólares a sus seguidores con nfc silver
very regrettable and has deleted the video he
muy lamentable y ha borrado el vídeo lo
has left it he
ha dejado
let her suck it does not come out it does not matter no
la dejaba chupar la no sale da igual no
and if he stops sucking it
y si la deja de chupar la
how are you people welcome to a new
qué tal gente bienvenidos a un nuevo
video for the channel
vídeo para el canal
how lucky for turbo plan that the
qué suerte para turbo plan que el botón
like button no longer shows the dislikes
de me gustas ya no enseñan los dislike
because this mother I am sure that it will be
porque esta madre estoy seguro que será
a [ __ ] lightsaber oh on this side
un [__] sable de luz uy de este lado
the sleeve and on this side the part of
el manguito y de este lado la parte de
the unemployment room there are many people who do not
la sala de paro hay mucha gente que no
give vila anymore the videos because as it is
le da vila ya los vídeos porque como ya
no longer seen because  it doesn't seem to him that this
no se ve porque no le da que hasta ahora
is the dumbest video of turbo plant so far and
es el vídeo más [__] de turbo plant y
look at what turbo plant has done wrong in the
mira qué turbo planta ha hecho mal los
videos seriously the map today and look at
vídeos en serio el mapa de hoy y mira
what turbo plant has made several
qué turbo plant ha hecho varios varios
bad videos but in this one he went too far from being an
malos vídeos pero en éste se pasó de
idiot to be so stupid he goes up
[__] para tanto de pendeja sube
accusing silver he says I want to open he
acusando a silver dice quiero abrir se
gets into legal trouble with this
mete en un problema legal con esto
man without silver he would like to find a
hombre sin silver se quisiera buscar un
lawyer in Spain and sue him yes
abogado en españa y demandarlo pues sí
but
pero
that he did the scam by putting
de que él haya hecho la estafa metiendo
information that he wasn't an [ __ ]
información que no era un cabrón
this mother was already five days ago
esta madre fue ya de hace cinco días
literally all the [ __ ]
literalmente todos los pinches canales
gossip channels already talked about this mother I
de chisme ya hablamos de esta madre yo
even put practically the entire
hasta metí prácticamente todo el
complete extract of the silver talking
extracto completo de the silver hablando
about juande what since the dead and
de lo de juande lo desde lo del dead y
not what against mother I mean you had all
no lo que contra madre o sea tenías todo
the [ __ ] context he could have stolen
el [__] contexto me pudo haber robado
the videos from me like he normally does he
los vídeos a mí como normalmente hace me
could have stolen the videos from me and
pudo haber robado los vídeos a mí y
made a good video but what he did
marcarse un buen vídeo pero lo que hizo
was I do
fue
n't know I'm going to use take the information
no sé voy a usar tomar la información
put that
meter ese la
third one in the hole and then take it out and
tercera por el hoyo y luego sacarla y
make a video no [ __ ] idea you can't see
hacer un vídeo ni [__] idea no se ve
metal he knows a lot and he went too far as a dick
metal sabe muchísimo y se pasó de [__]
good come to  see to know what that is well
buesa venir a ver a saber lo que eso es
almost almost like throwing [ __ ] at
pues casi casi como que tirándole [__]
the silver
el silver
and the other half well the last three
y la otra mitad bueno los últimos tres
minutes of being an idiot the one here doesn't lower it
minutos de [__] no lo baja
thanks and the idiot thing
el de la de aquí gracias y lo de [__]
doesn't lower it and it's like my son you are
no lo baja y es como mi hijo estás tú
to go around calling him an idiot someone you
para andarle diciendo [__] alguien lo
know it's like the best topic more tv planet he
sabes es como mejor tema más tv planeta
went too far because I tell you or rather he
se pasó de lanzado porque les digo o sea
already has all the [ __ ] context
ya tiene todo el [__] contexto en
everywhere gossip I talk about this I
todos lados chisme hablo de esto yo
talked about this he javi spoke from this
hablé de esto él javi habló desde este
pedrosa we all talk about this hair the
pedrosa todos hablamos de este pelo lo
only thing he had to do was test us
único que tenía que hacer era probarnos
in a [ __ ] script hui and that's it I know and
en [__] guión hui y ya está i know y
the Basque what he did very well he
el vasco lo que hizo muy bien
introduced it he took it out and said efe
se lo introducido lo sacó y dijo efe
this can be useful to me for plaster and
esto me puede servir para plasta y
disgusting candle really he went too far I'm not
asquerosa vela neta se pasó de lanzar no
going to watch the video because it's 17 minutes
voy a ver el vídeo porque son 17 minutos
well 18 small minutes thank you very much
bueno 18 minutos pequeños muchísimas
for the sub level 1 but what has he
gracias por la sub nivel 1 pero qué es
done as an example that's
lo que ha hecho de un ejemplo
why today I present to you my most
por eso que hoy les presento mi más
precious project to date the
preciado el proyecto hasta la fecha los
nfc thieves
rateros nfc
took out exactly 2000 then  like they
saco exactamente 2000 luego como si
were some kind of
fueran una especie de cartas
collectible cards or something like that so you
coleccionables o algo así para que lo
understand it well because I'm not going to
entendáis bien porque no me voy a poner
explain now what an ene efe is
a explicar ahora lo que es un ene efe
but let's just say in summary it's not worth
pero vamos en resumen que no vale con
downloading the image
descargarte la imagen hacer control
right click and copy and save the image no
derecho y copiar y guardar la imagen no
no when you buy with the nfc it's like they
no cuando tú compras en la nfc es como
give you a unique code and that
que te dan un código único y ese código
unique code certifies that you have that that
único certifica que tú tienes ese ese
card that collectible no of which
cromo ese coleccionable no de los cuales
2002-2003 come out no or these pixel rats
2002-2003 no o ratas de éstas de píxeles
and they sell for 80 euros each
y se venden a 80 euros cada uno
approximately 160 thousand euros in
aproximadamente pues 160 mil euros en
total no if we add the two thousand and it turns
total no si sumamos los dos mil y
out that well this is it's freaking out
resulta que bueno esto es es para flipar
that when he sold the 2002 he
que cuando cuando vendió los 2002 de
suddenly says on twitter that he's been
repente pone por twitter que le han
robbed that they've stolen all his money
robado que le han robado todo el dinero
and that it was a person who worked
y que ha sido una persona que trabajaba
with him a friend of a friend who
con él un amigo de un amigo que ha
took all the money or rather the 160,000
cogido todo el dinero o sea los 160.000
and took it and the thing is that right now
y se lo ha llevado y es que derecho no
the website doesn't even exist and obviously
existe ni la página web y obviamente
the rf test that bought the 2000
pues los rf test que compraron los 2000
rf test well  they are worth absolutely nothing
rf test pues no valen absolutamente nada
so you can get an idea in short he
para que os hagáis una idea en resumen
took it and said hey guys buy my nfcs it
cogió y dijo hay chicos comprad mis nfc
's that I've been
es que llevo un montón de tiempo
working on this project for a long time I don't know what the
trabajando en este proyecto no sé qué va
best thing will be and the day they are
a ser lo mejor y el día que se venden
all sold all the money disappears
todos desaparece todo el dinero
disappears in all the ene efe
desaparece en todos los ene efe
obviously in case the money disappears and
obviamente por si desaparece el dinero y
the website and everything no well the effects are
la página web y todo no pues los efectos
worthless and suddenly it's like oh I've
ya no valen nada y de repente es como ay
been robbed these types of scams and they
me han robado este tipo de estafas y
know the world of ene efe tests
conocen el mundo de las ene efe test
like ruth pool no and the thing is when
como ruth pool no y es que cuando la
people trust in a project no and buy
gente confía en un proyecto no y compra
everything well they buy all the ene efe tests
todo pues compra todas las ene efe test
of that project suddenly they just take it and
de ese proyecto de repente pues cogen y
disappear they delete absolutely everything and
desaparecen borran absolutamente todo y
leave with the money that's
se van con el dinero es
not
eso no
a pulse it has nothing to do with
es un pulso no tiene nada que ver con
the in ft in fact the FT project
las en ft de hecho el proyecto de ft
can also occur in the FT project
puede ocurrir también en proyecto de ft
haber pool roo for example you
haber pool roo por ejemplo
know this happens with crypts those
sabéis la esto pasa con las criptas
ways that are more crude the ones that
maneras esas que son más burdas las que
these ways those that they invent that are
estor maneras esas que inventan que son
the crypts currency of the squid game
las criptas moneda del juego del calamar
in fact I literally think there was one of the
de hecho literalmente creo que hubo una
game  of squid no that it went from being
del juego del calamar no que que pasó de
worth
valer
001 dollars to two thousand dollars and when
001 dólares a dos mil dólares y cuando
people with the squid game fashion
la gente con la moda el juego del
I play squid and people
calamar yo juego al calamar y la gente
buying squid game currency and
comprando moneda del juego del calamar y
when they go on for a day with people
cuando ellos siguen un día con la gente
putting in money it's worth two thousand dollars and
metiendo dinero vale dos mil dólares y
whoever is the owner of the
hace el que sea el propietario de las
stories like that
historias así
collects money and leaves and it's worth zero you
recogedor dinero y se pira y vale cero
understand these are the type of scam it
me entendéis estos son el tipo de estafa
is to know it implied a little tacky or it
es saberlo implicaba un poco cutre o lo
explains it a little [ __ ] it would be a little more
explica un poco [__] sería un poco más
extensive and more after the explanation but
extensa y más tras la explicación pero
well why so that you understand me to the
bueno para qué para que me entendáis a
country people to the wise
los a los campechanos a los sabios
free of okay
libres de vale
but well more or less I'm getting
pero bueno más o menos me voy haciendo
an idea of ​​the video let's see what my
una idea del vídeo a ver qué dijo mi
biggest hater said has my biggest
mayor hater tiene mi mayor gente
real people of pizza
de verdad de pizza
think a little bit idiots
piensa un poquito [__]
had of they tell him uninformed to the south to the
tuvieron de le dicen desinformado al sur
south no to the tour bonus to the south
al sur no al tour bono a sur
in his own tweet people giving it cane
en su propio tweet la gente dándole caña
to see it would have been powerful already air with
a ver hubiera estado potente ya aire con
the pretty ones that even speak I say it for
los bonitos que hasta habla lo digo para
the next one for the next with how beautiful the
la próxima para próxima con lo bonito
presentation was would have sirianni
que estaba presentación hubiera sirianni
that the year that would have put some
que el ao que hubiera puesto algunos
example clips that we will surely
clips de ejemplo que seguro que en
find on twitter,
twitter lo encontramos
surely on twitter if you put had a
seguro que en twitter si pones
silver plan some clean or
tuvo plan silver sale algún clean o
[Music]
[Música]
silver will sue turbo plan it is a video that is
silver demandará turbo plan es un vídeo
difficult to send to everyone flat eight
difíciles de mandar a todo planas ocho
minutes hello friends how were you my
minutos hola amigos como estaban mi
name is efrén and we already have gossip
nombre es efrén y ya tenemos chismecito
today silver will sue turbo
el día de hoy silver demandará a turbo
plan and also the person who took
plan y también a la persona que le quitó
all this money from him quality is attacked by
todo este dinero quality es atacado por
people for the controversial score that he
la gente por el polémico puntaje que le
gave to focus everything is wrong with me subscribe
dio a focus todo estoy mal suscríbete
like so that it reaches more people
dale like para que llegue a más personas
let's start with the first news and it
vamos a empezar con la primera noticia y
is that joaquín yesterday was in the juani
es que joaquín ayer estuvo en la juani
that the cup this cup wanted you
que la copa esta copa quiso
already know his name we are going to react to
ya saben su nombre vamos a reaccionar a
this because this is fresh fresh fresh
esto porque esto es fresco fresco fresco
for you facts tomorrow took advantage yes
para que ustedes hechos mañana aprovechó
yes I can file a lawsuit the kid
sí sí puedo meter una demanda el chavo
who was defaming me but what is not
que me estaba difamando pero lo que no
seen I do not feel that it is something youtube that is
se ve no siento que es algo youtube que
seen that they give youtube and not to put it in
se ve que dan youtube y no meterlo en
things that he wants to burn because in the end
cosas que quiere quemar pues al final
you know that I am working
ustedes saben que estoy trabajando
I am taking away the desire
estoy quitando la gana
discouraged a little yes of course there
desanimado un poco sí claro que sí
is nothing else to pull  verga goes up
no hay nada más que tirar de [__] sube
and there is this for he is defaming but it
y ahí está esto por está difamando pero
was so they find out what is happening with
fue se enteren de qué está pasando con
silver let's go for tomorrow I'll take advantage
silver vamos para mañana aprovecho
tomorrow I'll take advantage yes yes I can file the
mañana aprovecho sí sí puedo meter la
lawsuit the kid who was defaming me
demanda el chavo que me estaba difamando
but well no don't come back there are the
pero pues no que no se vuelvan están los
seven that is something youtube that it seems that they
siete que es algo youtube que se ve que
give youtube and not to put it in things and
dan youtube y no meterlo en cosas y
joseba also wants to burn well in the
joseba también quiere quemar pues al
end you know that I am working in the
final ustedes saben que estoy trabajando
end you know that I am
al final ustedes saben que yo estoy
taking the desire today we came to file the
quitando la gana hoy vinimos a hacer la
lawsuit against the guy who robbed us they told him they said that
demanda contra el vato que nos robo le
until Monday I have to
dijeron dijeron que hasta el lunes tengo
be there again with the agents that is why
que estar otra vez allí con los agentes
this starts because better not on
por eso inicia este porque mejor no el
Monday I did not come to turn on screen because
lunes no llegó a prender screen porque
today Monday I have to be the
hoy el lunes tengo que ser lo de los
agents here with the people of specials
agentes aquí con la gente de especiales
in the US and do less whether they are more or
en eeuu y hacer menos ya sean más o
less a man in we know more or less
menos un hombre en sabemos más o menos
everything
todo
[Music]
[Música]
on Monday the lawsuit is filed with the
el lunes se mete la demanda con la
person there he
persona ahí está él
is the one who has understood well what it is he has
es quien ha entendido bien qué es lo que
said that he will see what he will
ha dicho que va a ver qué va a
ask him if he can sue him or what will but that
preguntarle si puede demandarlo o qué va
although the things on
pero que aunque aunque las cosas de
youtube remain in  YouTube is that he
youtube se queden en youtube es que ha
said how do you do both things at the same time? I don't
dicho como las dos cosas a la vez no
understand, no,
entiendo no
and nothing is burning well on Twitter,
y nada están quemando bien en twitter a
turbo plan
turbo plan
would have been the re that would precarious you for
hubiera sido la re que te precaria para
an 18-minute video. I'm here now, I'm
un vídeo 18 minutos yo aquí ahora entero
not going to put a video now / 18 - to
no voy a poner un vídeo ahora / 18 - to
be it would have been incredible, Paula, to
be hubiera sido increíble paula
be a click away with some gem that there
ponerme a un clic con alguna joyita que
are surely gems that are cream
seguro que hay joyita que son crema
[Music]
[Música]